[
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Indian olympic Gold medalist?",
        "optionA": "Vijender Singh",
        "optionB": "Mary Kom",
        "optionC": "Abhinav Bindra",
        "optionD": "P.T.Usha",
        "answer": "Abhinav Bindra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country hosted the first commonwealth games?",
        "optionA": "USA",
        "optionB": "Canada",
        "optionC": "Mexico",
        "optionD": "Japan",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cricketer scored the first ever century?",
        "optionA": "Alfred Shaw",
        "optionB": "Dave Gregory",
        "optionC": "James Lillywhite",
        "optionD": "Charles Bannerman",
        "answer": "Charles Bannerman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country invented the sport fencing?",
        "optionA": "Germany",
        "optionB": "Spain",
        "optionC": "England",
        "optionD": "France",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the highest scorer in the history of LA Lakers?",
        "optionA": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
        "optionB": "LeBron James",
        "optionC": "Kobe Bryant",
        "optionD": "Magic Johnson",
        "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national sport of India?",
        "optionA": "Kabaddi",
        "optionB": "Cricket",
        "optionC": "Football",
        "optionD": "Hockey",
        "answer": "Hockey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the all time medals tally for India in olympics?",
        "optionA": "9 Gold 7 Silver 12 Bronze",
        "optionB": "6 Gold 8 Silver 11 Bronze",
        "optionC": "2 Gold 5 Silver 17 Bronze",
        "optionD": "2 Gold 8 Silver 15 Bronze",
        "answer": "9 Gold 7 Silver 12 Bronze"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sport is hosted in The Colosseum, Rome?",
        "optionA": "Chariot Races",
        "optionB": "Gladiator Battles",
        "optionC": "Bull Fighting",
        "optionD": "Knighthood Competition",
        "answer": "Gladiator Battles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first ever captain of the Indian cricket team?",
        "optionA": "C K Nayudu",
        "optionB": "Mansur Ali Khan Pataudi",
        "optionC": "Polly Umrigar",
        "optionD": "Lala Amarnath",
        "answer": "C K Nayudu"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which year was archery considered as a sport?",
        "optionA": "1899",
        "optionB": "1900",
        "optionC": "1901",
        "optionD": "1903",
        "answer": "1900"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first man to win a marathon race in olympics?",
        "optionA": "Arthur Blake",
        "optionB": "Gyula Kellner",
        "optionC": "Edwin Flack",
        "optionD": "Spyridon Louis",
        "answer": "Spyridon Louis"
    },
    {
        "question": "When were the athletics introduced in olympics?",
        "optionA": "1892",
        "optionB": "1896",
        "optionC": "1900",
        "optionD": "1904",
        "answer": "1896"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two countries participated in the first ever cricket test match?",
        "optionA": "England vs West Indies",
        "optionB": "Australia vs West Indies",
        "optionC": "Australia vs England",
        "optionD": "England vs India",
        "answer": "Australia vs England"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the highest runs scorer in the history of baseball?",
        "optionA": "Pete Rose",
        "optionB": "T Y Cobb",
        "optionC": "Rickey Henderson",
        "optionD": "Hank Aaron",
        "answer": "Rickey Henderson"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country introduced short put?",
        "optionA": "Norway",
        "optionB": "Denmark",
        "optionC": "Finland",
        "optionD": "Scotland",
        "answer": "Scotland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first Indian woman to win a medal in olympics?",
        "optionA": "Saina Nehwal",
        "optionB": "Mary Kom",
        "optionC": "P T Usha",
        "optionD": "Karnam Malleswari",
        "answer": "Karnam Malleswari"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did India play their first test match against Pakistan?",
        "optionA": "1951",
        "optionB": "1952",
        "optionC": "1953",
        "optionD": "1954",
        "answer": "1952"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who scored the first ever goal in the history of FIFA World Cup?",
        "optionA": "Sándor Kocsis",
        "optionB": "Guillermo Stábile",
        "optionC": "Lucien Laurent",
        "optionD": "Jimmy Douglas",
        "answer": "Lucien Laurent"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the longest jump ever in the history of long jump?",
        "optionA": "8.5m",
        "optionB": "8.7m",
        "optionC": "8.9m",
        "optionD": "9.1m",
        "answer": "8.9m"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the firct U19 Cricket World Cup?",
        "optionA": "India",
        "optionB": "Australia",
        "optionC": "England",
        "optionD": "Pakistan",
        "answer": "India"
    }
]